CV Doubts:

1. How to do the image resizing.
	- use cv2.resize, mean and normalize by norm of image. 
	DONE
2. KNN from scipy for predict_kNN, as this is imported we will have to do that.
	- kNN can be used for supervised leased weights.
	KNN DOES THE VOTING BY THEMSELF
3. compute_dsift doesn’t have stride and size parameters.
	- Use inside function, No issues
4. What input should build_visual_dictionary should have.
		- give the final feature vector not list.
5. Should Compute bow be happening for All the images at once or one by one.
	- Compute bow is for every image